youjustgetme.com 2014-04-25

# YouJustGetMe | Are Personality Impressions Accurate?

##  Privacy Policy - YouJustGetMe.com 

###  Last Updated: January 14, 2008 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the YouJustGetMe.com [ Terms of Use](http://www.youjustgetme.com/index.php?page=terms). For the purposes of this Agreement, those who use YouJustGetMe.com are "Users." This group includes anyone who registers for YouJustGetMe.com, who are "Members." Each time you use the Site, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using the services on our Site. Please remember that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we don't own or control or to people that we don't employ or manage. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifying information about you. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by YouJustGetMe.com (the "Site") and not to any other websites linked to or from YouJustGetMe.com. 

##  COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

**1.1. When You Register**

During the process of registering to become a Member on the Site, you may be required to provide personally identifying information ("Personal Information") such as your name, email address, and password. You may also be required to provide information that does not personally identify you such as a display name, birth date, gender, and postal code. **The default functionality of the Site (excluding any content that Users post or link to on other websites) will never display the Personal Information you provide at registration to other Users of the Site.** However, as provided in the YouJustGetMe.com Terms of Use, you are solely responsible for all information you post on YouJustGetMe.com, communicate to other Users, or post on other websites that you link to or from YouJustGetMe.com, including information that would personally identify you. By using YouJustGetMe.com, you also understand and agree that Users may use your real name to locate your information and/or to view your profile depending on your profile settings. 

**1.2. When You Browse the Site**

 **Log Files**

Like most standard website servers, we use and maintain the information that we obtain from your browser on our server logs. This information can include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), and other data. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may associate this information with your Personal Information to resolve technical issues and support security for our Users. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use the Site. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and are read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Our primary use of cookies will be to improve your experience on the Site. For example, storing a cookie on your computer may allow you to login without typing the registered email address and password. We may also use cookies to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. If you do not want these cookies stored on your computer you can reject cookies by modifying your browser setting accordingly (each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to access products and services that we offer that require you to "login" or "sign in". Please also note that certain types of emails available through the Site may automatically log you into the Site and/or set new cookies when you click on the links in the emails and that you may need to manually remove such cookies if you do not want them to be set on your computer. 

**Web Beacons**

A web beacon (also known as a clear gif) is a tiny graphic with a unique identifier that is placed on a web page or within an email. It is similar in function to a cookie, and is used to collect a limited set of information, such as a cookie number, time and date of page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. YouJustGetMe.com and its third party advertisers may use web beacons to compile aggregate statistics about which advertisements and promotions Users have seen and how Users responded to them. This information helps us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. In addition, we may use web beacons in our promotional email messages to count how many messages and which emails have been opened and acted upon. This use allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and our marketing campaigns. YouJustGetMe.com does associate web beacons to individual Member personal information for internal purposes only, in an effort to understand our Member's individual preferences with our email products. 

**1.3. When You Build a Personal Profile**

YouJustGetMe.com has created tools to enable our Users to not only see what other Users think of you, but also allow you to provide information about yourself. You can use these tools to build a personal profile to share as much or as little information about yourself as you wish. �You may also set your profile to be viewable by only friends who know your real name, only registered Site Members, or all Internet users. Except as otherwise noted when you use a specific profile tool, all information that you add to your profile is publicly viewable by other Internet users and may be included in the Site "search" tool. **For this reason, please use care in providing information that you may not want to publicly disclose. To protect the privacy of our Users, YouJustGetMe.com does not allow the public posting of personal contact information.** As provided in our Terms of Use, YouJustGetMe.com may use the information you provide in your profile in a variety of YouJustGetMe.com products, features, and emails. This enables us to provide you with information in a more personalized fashion. 

**1.4. When You Use the Message Center**

For registered Members, we have developed a [ Message Center ](http://www.youjustgetme.com/index.php?page=message_center) that uses a "double-blind" messaging system, which hides the personal email addresses given during registration to protect the privacy of both the sender and receiver. You may prevent another Member from sending future messages to you via the Message Center by clicking "Block" next to him or her user name while viewing a message. If you block another Member, you will also no longer be able to send messages to him or her. 

When using the Message Center, it is up to you to choose when you are comfortable disclosing your email address, or any other contact information, to others. YouJustGetMe.com respects the privacy of Member communications sent through the Message Center and does not read or disclose those communications unless we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of YouJustGetMe.com Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law enforcement. 

**1.5. Invitations and Other Communications to Non-Users**

YouJustGetMe.com Members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. YouJustGetMe.com stores the email addresses that Members provide so that the recipient's ratings of the Member who sent the invitation may be shown to both parties, and so both parties may earn [ Contribution Credits ](http://www.youjustgetme.com/index.php?page=contributions) for these activities, and also to send reminders of the invitations. **YouJustGetMe.com does not sell or display the email addresses of those who are invited to use the Site or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and up to three (3) reminders.** Recipients of invitations from YouJustGetMe.com may send an email to [ memberships@youjustgetme.com ](mailto:memberships@youjustgetme.com?subject=removal%20request) with the words "removal request" in the subject line to request the removal of their information from our database or to prevent YouJustGetMe.com invitations and other messages from being sent. 

**1.6. When you purchase more Contribution Credits**

YouJustGetMe.com works in collaboration with PayPal.com to enable you to purchase Contribution Credits. Any information that you provide during this transaction with PayPal is governed by PayPal's own [ privacy policy ](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). Users concerned about submitting information to PayPal should review PayPal's privacy policy. **YouJustGetMe.com does not collect, receive, store, or have access to your personal financial information such as credit card information, PayPal account information, bank account information, or billing information.** YouJustGetMe.com receives from PayPal.com only your name, postal address, email address, and the quantity of Contribution Credits you have ordered. This information is used only internally, and it is not sold to other parties or displayed. 

**1.7. When You Participate in Surveys**

From time to time, we may request information from our Users via surveys relating to our services or on behalf of our affiliates, scientific collaborators, or third-party advertisers. When you participate in a survey, we may or may not request contact information (such as your name and email address) or demographic information (such as your zip code, age or income level). YouJustGetMe.com conducts surveys in order to target advertising and content and to better understand Users' needs and opinions. YouJustGetMe.com may share, in aggregate form, information it collects from these surveys with its advertisers, partners, affiliates and the general public, but will not share survey information containing personally identifiable information with any third party without your prior consent. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, such that you have the choice of whether you wish to disclose the requested information. However, we encourage our Users to participate in these surveys as they provide us with important information that helps us to improve our services or services that may offered on our Site or via email by our affiliates or third-party advertisers. 

**1.8. When You or Third Parties Contact Us**

If you contact YouJustGetMe.com by phone, email, letter, or via a form on the Site, we may keep a record of such correspondence. Thus, if you report an issue with the Site, we may collect such information in a file specific to you.� Moreover, if you contact us through our feedback area, we may require your name and email address in order to send you a reply. Additionally, if other Users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may keep the information in a file specific to you. 

**1.9. How We May Supplement your Personal Information**

In order for us to properly fulfill our obligations to our Members, it may be necessary for us from time to time to supplement the information we receive through your use of the Site with information from third party resources. For example, we may obtain updated email address information from email-change-of-address vendors or purchase third party marketing data and address information and add it to our existing database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think you would be interested in. 

##  SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOUJUSTGETME.COM COLLECTS 

**2.1. Confidentiality**

YouJustGetMe.com only shares your Personal Information with others when we have your permission or under the types of circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. In addition, we limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or to do their jobs. 

**2.2. Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to Users by YouJustGetMe.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by YouJustGetMe.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**2.3. Scientific Research**

By using YouJustGetMe.com, you agree to allow us or our scientific collaborators to use the information from you and your experience on the Site to continue our research into how people perceive others. **All researchers who receive data from the Site will be required to obtain approval by their home institutions to conduct research with human subjects, and all data provided to such researchers will contain no information that would personally identify you as a User of the Site.** At present, researchers at the University of Texas at Austin have obtained Institutional Review Board approval ([click here](http://www.youjustgetme.com/images_web/UTIRB6-5-51approval.pdf)) to receive and analyze data from this Site. This research may be published in academic journals usually in aggregate form that describes the behavior of groups not individuals. You can find out more about the Federal Guidelines observed by the American Psychological Association for conducting research with human subjects at: [ http://www.apa.org/science/research/reglaws.html ](http://www.apa.org/science/research/reglaws.html). 

**2.4. Service Providers**

We may sometimes use a third party to provide specific services on our behalf, including sending emails to our Members, conducting member surveys, processing transactions or performing statistical analysis of our services. In these cases, we may provide certain personal information, such as your name and email address and other financial information necessary for the service to be provided. However, these third parties are required to maintain the confidentiality of this information and are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using this information for any other purposes. 

YouJustGetMe.com may provide certain portions of your Personal Information, such as your email address or name, back to your ISP if we have an existing advertising relationship with them. This is done to allow them to target or discontinue your exposure to our advertisements, once you have become a participating member of our Site. As part of our agreement with your ISP, they will be required to maintain this information in a confidential manner and use it solely for the purpose described in this Policy. 

##  CHANGING CORRECTING OR REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION 

YouJustGetMe.com provides you with ways in which you can update your Personal Information. To make changes to your Personal Information, please login to the Site and go to your [ My Account ](http://www.youjustgetme.com/index.php?page=account) page. Here you may change such information as your first and last name, display name, postal code, and password and communication settings. You may also change your settings that determine whether your profile may be seen by no one, only registered Members, or all Internet users. 

**If you wish to terminate your registered Membership at any time, for any reason, send an email from the address you registered with to[ memberships@youjustgetme.com ](mailto:memberships@youjustgetme.com?subject=terminate) with the word "terminate" entered in the subject line. Allow five (5) business days for removal of your information from the Site. ** Upon removal of membership from the Site, we may retain your Personal Information for a period of time in our internal databases and systems. 

##  THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION 

We have instituted physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to store and maintain your Personal Information in a secure environment. You may also be required to use a password to access certain pages on the Site where certain types of your Personal Information can be changed or deleted. It is therefore important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and emails which we may send you and to your computer. You take full responsibility for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. Furthermore, while we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. We cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your Personal Information from the threats of tomorrow. You should also be aware that despite our efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we are not in a position to guarantee that your Personal Information will be secure under all circumstances. 

##  A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT THE PRIVACY OF MINORS 

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, fair information practices and various state laws, we will not knowingly allow children under the age of fourteen to become Members.� If we later learn that a child under the age of fourteen is a Member, then that child's Membership will be terminated. We collect, use and disclose information about minors aged fourteen to seventeen in the same manner as we do for adults.� YouJustGetMe.com believes that it is especially important to protect children's privacy online and encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to participate and monitor their Internet activity.� If you are under 18, you must first obtain your parent's permission before using the site. We do not filter advertisements or other content that children may receive, such that they could receive content and materials that are inappropriate for children. 

We only allow child-to-child contact and adult-to-adult contact via the Site and strictly prohibit adult-to-child contact. Thus, Members who are eighteen (18) and older may only send messages via the Message Center to other Members who are eighteen (18) and older; and Members who are aged fourteen (14) to seventeen (17) may only send messages via the Message Center to other Members who are age fourteen (14) to seventeen (17). The Site will not allow Members to initiate, nor deliver any Message sent by a Member who is eighteen (18) and older to a Member who is fourteen (14) to seventeen (17), or vice versa. 

##  CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

YouJustGetMe.com may modify the Privacy Policy from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by YouJustGetMe on the YouJustGetMe.com Website. You agree to be bound to any changes to this Privacy Policy when you use the YouJustGetMe services after any such modification is posted. It is therefore important that you review this Agreement regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If there are significant changes to the Privacy Policy which may affect the compilation, release or dissemination of your information contained on the Site we will notify you at the email address you provided upon registering and/or by posting a notice on YouJustGetMe.com for a period of thirty (30) days. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [ memberships@youjustgetme.com ](mailto:memberships@youjustgetme.com?subject=privacy) with the word "privacy" entered in the subject line.
